<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>UNICEF Mentorship on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</title>
    <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory-staging/unicef-mentorship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in UNICEF Mentorship on UNICEF O.S. Inventory</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Creative Commons BY-SA 4.0. Site theme maintained by UNICEF. Original theme, Dot, created by ThemeFisher.</copyright><atom:link href="https://unicef.github.io/inventory-staging/unicef-mentorship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workflow: Update external UNICEF metrics</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory-staging/unicef-mentorship/workflow-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory-staging/unicef-mentorship/workflow-metrics/</guid>
      <description>Open Source data and analytics are used across multiple tools and documents for talking about Venture Fund portfolio companies. When updating data sources in official UNICEF portals, follow this process for the quickest way of updating metrics.
  Open data input source (e.g. Sharepoint doc, Google Doc shared with company, etc.)
  Open Cauldron.io dashboard for company/project
  Look at annual ranges first before doing quarterly ranges. Some metrics need to be collected manually for annual ranges:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workplan: Bridge Fund cohort</title>
      <link>https://unicef.github.io/inventory-staging/unicef-mentorship/workplan-bridge-funding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://unicef.github.io/inventory-staging/unicef-mentorship/workplan-bridge-funding/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents 1. Mission 2. Vision 3. Community 4. Timeline 4.1. Q1 4.2. Q2 4.3. Q3 4.4. Q4   5. References   This page documents the workplan requirements for the Bridge Fund cohort of the UNICEF Venture Fund. These graduation expectations are in place for UNICEF grantees receiving follow-on funding from UNICEF. See the table of contents for navigating.
 1. Mission Bridging humanitarian Open Source works and communities to the wider Open Source ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
